ACTWU's National Textile Recruitment and Training Program Records 5619/034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Total Terminations Column C, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Total Participants Column B, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Control Sheet, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- General Contract File Control Sheet, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Quarterly Reports, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Total Participants Column B, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Roselyn Manufacturing Co., Inc. Graph Sheet, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Roselyn Manufacturing Co., Inc. Intakes, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Roselyn Manufacturing Co., Inc. Coordinator Activity Reports, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Roselyn Manufacturing Company, Inc. Intakes, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Check Account Resolution, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- Avtex Fibers Program no.5, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- Amerbelle Graph Sheet, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Amerbelle Union Correspondences, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 78)
- Amerbelle Contract, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 79)
- Amerbelle Coordinator Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 80)
- Synthetic Apprenticeship, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 81)
- Charleston- CETA Worker, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Charleston Social Service, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 83)
- Bellefonte Corp. Scottsboro, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Avtex, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- Avtex Front Royal, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 86)
- Avtex Fibers Synthetic Division, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 87)
- Jonathan Temple Contract, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Jonathan Temple Intakes, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Glenmore Plastics Graph Sheet, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Glenmore Plastics Correspondence, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Quilting Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Quilting Co., Inc. Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Quilting Co. Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Quilting Intakes, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Brooklyn Quilting Intakes, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Union Plastic Company Trainee Record, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Union Plastic Company Kearny, New Jersey, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Clifton Yarn Mills Contract, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Clifton Heights Yarn Mills Graph Sheet, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Clifton Yarn Mills Graph Sheet Trainee Record, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Everlon Fabrics Trainee Record, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Everlon Fabrics Graph Sheets Intakes, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Everlon-Closter Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Everlon-Closter Graph Sheet, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Ballet Fabrics Intakes, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Ballet Fabrics Coordinator Activity Reports, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Ballet Fabrics Trainee Record, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Ballet Fabrics, Inc., 1979 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Ballet Fabrics Communications, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Ballet Fabrics Contract, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Ballet Fabrics Intakes and Graph Sheet, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Courtaulds No. America, Inc. Coordinator Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Courtaulds No. America, Inc. Intakes Contract Union Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Glenmore Plastics, Inc. Brooklyn, NY Contract, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Glenmore Plastics Graph Sheet, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Glenmore Plastics Union Correspondence, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Modern Filters, Inc. W. Haverstraw, N.Y., 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Glenmore Plastics, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Gurney Mfg. Div. Graph Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Gurney Mfg. Div. Union Correspondence, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Gurney Mfg. Div. Company Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Gurney Mfg. Div. Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Gurney Training Company, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Gurney Manufacturing, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Packaging Systems Corp. Division Trainee Record Graph Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Packaging Systems Corp. Packaging Division (Correspondence), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Packaging Systems Corp. Packaging Division Contract, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Packaging Systems Corp. Packaging Division Intakes, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Packaging Systems Packaging Division Graph Sheet, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Packaging Systems Company Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Packaging Systems Fasco Div. Graph Sheet, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Packaging Systems Fasco Intakes, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Packaging Systems Fasco Graph Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Packaging Systems Fasco Correspondence, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Fleisher Finishing, Inc. NTRTP Retention Survey, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Fleisher Finishing, Inc. Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Fleisher Finishing, Inc. Coordinator Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Modern Filters Correspondence, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Philadelphia Felt Company Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Chromatex, Inc., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Gold Mills, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Everlon Clifton Pending, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Quachita Finishing Company, Inc. Monroe, La., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Quachita Finishing Company, Inc. Coordinator Activity Reports, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Quachita Finishing Company, Inc., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Summergrade Graph Sheet, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Summergrade Coordinator Activity Report, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Classroom Program - Narrative Report, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Terminations Column C, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Total Participants [folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  3/31/1981
- Total Participants [folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Total Completions, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Quarterly Reports, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Control Sheet, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Classroom Program Narrative Report, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  12/31/1980
- Quarterly Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Total Participants, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Terminations Column C, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Total Completions, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Control Sheet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Total Completions, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  9/30/1980
- Terminations, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Control Sheet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Total Participants, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Quarterly Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Quarterly Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Classroom Program - Narrative Report, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- C. Cosentino Co. Contract, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- C. Cosentino Intakes, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- C. Cosentino Co. Union Correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- C. Cosentino Co. Graph Sheet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Craftex Philadelphia, Pa Contract, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Craftex Philadelphia, Pa Intakes, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Craftex Philadelphia, Pa Union Correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Craftex Philadelphia, Pa Graph Sheet, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Graber Ind. Contract Saginaw, Michigan, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Jeffries Processors Philadelphia, Pa Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Jeffries Processors Philadelphia, Pa Coordinator Activity Report, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Jomac Contract Warrington, Pa, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Jomac, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Jomac Intakes Warrington, Pa, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Kalkstein Intakes, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Kalkstein Graph Sheet, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Kalkstein Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Lorbrook Corporation, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Lorbrook Corporation Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Lorbrook Corporation Intakes, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Lorbrook Corporation Union Correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Lorbrook Corporation Coordinator Activity Reports, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Mosseri National Industry Contract, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Mosseri National Industry Intakes, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Mosseri National Industry Graph Sheet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Mosseri National Industry Union Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Nova Knitting Mills Contract Farmingdale, NJ, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Nova Knitting Mills Graph Sheet Farmingdale, NJ, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Nova Knitting Mills Company Correspondence Farmingdale, NJ, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Penn-Wilton Carpet Mills Philadelphia, Pa Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Penn-Wilton Carpet Mills Graph Sheet Philadelphia, Pa, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Penn-Wilton Carpet Graph Sheet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Putnam-Herzel Finishing Company Contracts, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Ronitex Graph Sheet, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Ronitex Contract, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Contract (Fleischer Finishing), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Graph Sheet (Fleischer Finishing), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Coordinator Activity Report (Fleischer Finishing), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Correspondence (Fleischer Finishing), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Hugh Nelson Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Hugh Nelson Union Correspondence, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Hugh Nelson Graph Sheet, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Textile Prints, Contracts Branford, Conn., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Textile Prints, Intakes Branford, Conn., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 72)
- Textile Prints, Graph Sheet Branford, Conn., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 73)
- Textile Prints, Coordinator Activity Reports Branford, Conn., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Roselyn Screen Print, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- Roselyn Screen Print Invoices, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 76)
- Scalamandre, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- Scalamandre Contract, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- Scalamandre Company Correspondence, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Cohoes Sleeping Bag Company Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- Cohoes Sleeping Bag Company Intakes, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 81)
- Cohoes Sleeping Bag Company (Graph Sheet plus Status of Training Report), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 82)
- El Paso Joint Board, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 83)
- GTA Joint Board, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 84)
- Beattie Manufacturing Company, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 85)
- Graber, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 86)
- Loray Fabrics, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 87)
- Narrows, Va. ACTWU, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 88)
- Columbia Carpet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 89)
- Master Craft Inactive, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 90)
- Pennsylvania Carpet Mills, N.C., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 91)
- Southern New England Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 92)
- Universal Needle Craft Training Forms, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 93)
- Universal Needle Craft, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 94)
- Bama Mills Fabrics America, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 95)
- Sanlam Corp. Contract, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 96)
- Worth Textile Sylvester, Ga., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 97)
- New Proposal Contract 6, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 98)
- OJT Info, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 99)
- Program no.5 Local Coord. Expenses, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 100)
- NTRTP 3rd Contract, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 101)
- NTRTP 3rd Contract, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 102)
- NTRTP 3rd Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 103)
- NTRTP 1st Quarter Activity, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 104)
- NTRTP, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 105)
- Front Royal December Quarter, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 106)
- NTRTP Mail, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 107)
- Race & Sex Characteristics, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 108)
- Union Plastic Company Kearny, New Jersey, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 109)
- Warrenton Woolen Incorporated, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 110)
- A. Wimpfheimer & Bro. Inc., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 111)
- Zamax Mfg. Company, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 112)
- Philadelphia Felt Co., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 113)
- Putnam-Herzl Finishing Company, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 114)
- Quachita Finishing Company, Inc., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 115)
- Riveredge Warping Co., 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 116)
- W. Summergrade & Sons, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 117)
- NTRTP Receipts, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Metrics Teachers, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Local 1855 Columbus, Ga., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Hartwell Street, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Highlander Center (GED), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Service & Allied Industry Joint Board (School), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Central Alabama Joint Board Local 1840, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Dyers & Finishers Local 2052, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- NTRTP Receipts, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Joint Board (Luke Martin-ESL), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Joint Board (School), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Ruttenberg Friedman Kilgallon Gutchess & Assoc., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Anchor Dye & Finishing Co. Inc., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Ballet Fabrics, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Chromatex, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Clifton Yarn Mills Kearny, New Jersey, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- C. Consentino Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- El Paso Joint Board, ACTWU Sewing Mach. Mechanics, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Everlon Fabrics, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Fleisher Finishing, Inc., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Jamac Incorporated, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Jefferies Processors, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Kalkstein Silk Mills Paterson, New Jersey, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Hugh Nelson Columbia Carpet, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Packaging Systems Corp., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Domestic Apparel Program Review, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Education and Training Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- JTR Subcontractor Contract, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- JTR, Inc. Trainee Progress Report, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- JTR, Inc. Response to Request, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- JTR, Inc. Proposal, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- JTR, Inc. Research and Development Program, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 32)